CONNECT WITH ME!

Portfolio: henrybernardin.com

Github: github.com/henry-bernardin
Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/henry-bernardin
Email: henry.bernardin@gmail.com

Phone: 347-236-5657

Address: 5538 Whitty Ln, Brooklyn, NY 11203

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Front-End Web Developer/Designer, with six year plus program management experience, whom enjoys working with others to achieve an objective on time and with excellence. Seeking to assume a role which will facilitate continued personal and professional growth.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Responsive Web Design
- Testing/Debugging
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- JavaScript
- iQuery
- Node.js
- Version Control (Git/Github)
- SEO and Google Analytics
- Web UI/UX Design
- Cross-Browser Compatibility
- Cross-Browse - WordPress
- React.js
- Program Management

CERTIFICATIONS

-Freecodecamp.org Responsive Web Design Given Dec. 17, 2018

-Chingu.io Chingu Voyage 12 Given Nov. 17, 2019

HENRY BERNARDIN

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER/DESIGNER

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

Freelance | Dec. 2018 to present

- Communicate with clients to deliver quality web projects, and follow ups to ensure that the customer is satisfied with their product
- Develop, and deploy custom Front-End HTML, CSS, & Javascript websites
- Configure domain names and hosting through Netlify.com

PROGRAM MANAGER

Cerebral Palsy Associations of New York State | Oct. 2016 to present

- Responsible for awareness and compliance with all state and federally mandated requirements pertaining to the program (OMRDD, OSHA, COA, Medicaid, HIPAA, etc.)
- Documentation, review and submission of all financial accounts, ledgers associated with personal allowance, earned income and members in house ledgers for cash on hand, including staff payroll, and site expenditures
- Ensure the proper reporting, investigation and review of all incidents relative to OPWDD Part 624 regulations and the Justice Center

ASSISTANT PROGRAM MANAGER

Catholic Charities Neighborhood Services | Jul. 2014 to Oct. 2016

- Supervised and ensured completion of apartment inspections and fire drills
- Provided support in order to ensure constant audit readiness and regulatory compliance of all records, services, and maintenance issues
- Responsible for assisting in training of all policies, procedures in accordance with OPwDD regulations and guidelines

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK- BROOKLYN COLLEGE

B.S., Double Major in Health Nutrition Sciences & Psychology

- Aug. 2006 to May 2010